Hello friends, hello technologists,
our topic today is
that you have this number 10m bike or car,
then you believe in your Hinduism,
okay, so what happens if
you are not able to get the print out on it or you do
not get the print out, that is, the printer is
from the company, then you can join it again with the return no. You
can understand the police in this, so Asman is telling
in our video, where you
push something, put ghee in it, how do you do it,
then tell me the next row that dad, you
can install it of whichever kind, so let's go to the most successful
religion, here you have to type CSC
login, so whatever
side effect you have done here,
open it here, then
tell me how are your ID and password here, so now
you can see that we have pressed here, there
is a cylinder, so now what do you have to do, you
can enter insurance etc. here, after that you have the
insurance option here  Click on it and you will get it
there, after that whatever you want to
download the certificate of the page year, you can
use it here, you can take turmeric powder
written here and ginger powder also
here, that is why today we are seeing that
motor company only cycle, you have
kept third party here, you can quickly see it here
and if we motor company means
party also, then click on the left party
hunter,
you have trusted half the company here,
click on it, then
mostly from here you will get one, the youth which is
written here is active so that the
body here, you can see that this is the
specialty, that is the essay, sit here for a few minutes,
service charge, this chapter will show you today,
we have written SSC here, with this
border children should
click on it here, after that as soon as you
click, it will appear on your face, this is the
work, so see, on biscuits, if you want to do
marriage etc., you can use it here, let me
tell you clearly, today we will
tell you how to resolve your doubt, then
here I will show you the option
Extract the juice from the masturbation business above, so come
here my partner, click on it a little
and you have done a little bit of thinking about it, in
which I am
also proud of it, I will put this
incident date
loot, after that here you have
your product, I had beaten this motor, this motor, the
police is already here, so for the motor from here,
after that which is your policy, it is for two
wheeler, Dual app is sitting, okay, the
person who has the right like Mi, type it here, it is
appropriate for you here, my two
wheeler letter here, you can see here
that your two love first work,
click on this tube, apart from this, if you search, then the
dictum which you will search here,
this application will also open in front of you,
so here we can see the option of our Jaibu and Police,
apply here,
download your police time,
here you take note of it, you
can see that this is our okay,
it has been downloaded here, in this
way you can
also download the police on your debit card easily, so
please like  And don't forget to share,
thank you.